Usman Ali

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

PHP Laravel Framework

Basic of React JS

Basic Redux & Redux saga

SQL skills

PERSONAL SKILLS

Attention to detail

Good analytical skills

Goals orientated

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address : Tekdari Khwaza

khela Swat

Email:

usmanalitikdari@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/Usmanalis bbu

Mobile No:

+923489591391

DOB: 03/05/1996

Nationality: Pakistani

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A highly resourceful, innovative, and competent Laravel developer with extensive experience in the database design and coding of websites specifically in Laravel and basic of React Js. Possessing considerable knowledge of the development of web applications and scripts using PHP programming language and JavaScript.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Basic Work In INJAZAT SOFTWARE (Saudi Arabia), (Remotely)
LARAVEL AND REACT DEVLOPER December 2020 - Present

Responsible for the technical and administration aspects of the companies React Js. Also the first point of call for providing technical support as well as specialist technical input.

Duties:

- Develop custom API layer to handle all CRUD transactions, JWT token management and implemented interceptors to embed custom headers.
- To Manage Redux-Saga with Immutable Js

SKYLINE WEB SOLUTION (Local)

LARAVEL DEVELOPER
Microsoft Office 365

June 2019 – November 2020

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Able to plan the structure of a database
- Ability to multi-task, react quickly to shifting priorities and meet deadlines.
- Continuously monitoring industry trends, technologies and standards.
- Excellent attention to detail both front and back end.
- Solid web development experience using OOP, PHP, LARAVEL, PYTHON, MySQL, JavaScript,, HTML and CSS.
- Enough Skill In Word, Power Point and Excel.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

BS Hons In Computer Science
Shaheed Benazir Bhutto University Sheringal Dir(Upper)
2016 – oct-2020

FSC: Pre Engineering Khyber Public School and College Khwaza khela Swat 2013 - 2015